Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - Moore, Melba - Take my love, 1981; SR-22452; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          Catalog # SPRO-9678; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9678-Z-1
          EMI America
        - Moore, Melba - Pick me up, I'll dance, 1978; SR-22453; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          Catalog # 28-50665; A-side Matrix # XSS 165375-1A
        - Moore, Melba - Love the one I'm with (a lot of love), 1986; SR-22454; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          Catalog # SPRO-9717; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9717-100291-Z2
        - Moore, Melba - Underlove, 1982; SR-22455; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22456. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO-9902; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9902-98482C-Z1
        - Moore, Melba - Underlove, 1982; SR-22456; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22455. 2 copies.
        - Moore, Melba - You stepped into my life; There's no other like you, 1978; SR-22457; Moore, Melba (Box 363)
          Catalog # 28-50601; A-side Matrix # XSS-164891-2A
        - Moore, René - All or nothing, 1988; SR-22458; Moore, René (Box 363)
          Catalog # 871 065-1; A-side Matrix # 871-065-1-AS HRM
        - Moore, Rudy Ray - The third Rudy Ray Moore album-The cockpit, 1971; SR-22459; Moore, Rudy Ray (Box 363)
          Catalog # KST 006; A-side Matrix # KST 006 A
          Kent
        - Moore, Rudy Ray - The 10th Rudy Ray Moore album-Dolemite is another crazy nigger, 1988; SR-22460; Moore, Rudy Ray (Box 363)
          Catalog # COMS 1115; A-side Matrix # KST-022-1
          Comedian International Enterprises
        - Moore, Tina - Never gonna let you go (the Hurley dance mixes), 1995; SR-22461; Moore, Tina (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22462. Double album.
          Catalog # 72392 78019-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 78019-1A
          Scotti Bros Records
        - Moore, Tina - Never gonna let you go (the Hurley dance mixes), 1995; SR-22462; Moore, Tina (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22461. Double album.
          Catalog # 72392 78019-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 78019-1C
        - Moorish Delta 7 - Rowdy, 2002; SR-22463; Moorish Delta 7; Judge Dreadi (Box 363)
          Catalog # Rights EV 004; A-side Matrix # RIGHTS EV 004 A1
          Seven Entertainment
          Birmingham, United Kingdom
        - M.O.P. - World famous, 1997; SR-22464; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          Catalog # RPROLP 0542; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0542 A
        - M.O.P. - Stick to ya gunz; Brownsville, 1996; SR-22465; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0484; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0484 A
        - M.O.P. - Pain; Big boy game, 2005; SR-22466; M.O.P.; Marxmen (Box 363)
          Catalog # KOC-12-5825; A-side Matrix # KOC-12-5825/A
        - M.O.P. - Dead & gone; Stick to ya gunz, 1996; SR-22467; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          Catalog # 88561-1568-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1586-1 A
        - M.O.P. - Dead & gone; Stick to ya gunz, 1996; SR-22468; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22469. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 88561-1568-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1568-1 A
        - M.O.P. - Dead & gone; Stick to ya gunz, 1996; SR-22469; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22468. 2 copies.
        - M.O.P. - 4 alarm blaze, 1988; SR-22470; M.O.P. (Box 363)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0792; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0792 A RE1
        - MOR - NLP (disc one), 2001; SR-22471; MOR (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22472. Double album.
          Catalog # RB030; A-side Matrix # RB 030 A
          Royal Bunker
          West Berlin, Germany
        - MOR - NLP (disc two), 2001; SR-22472; MOR (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22471. Double album.
          Catalog # RB030; A-side Matrix # RB 030 C
        - More, Billy - Go dance, 1979; SR-22473; More, Billy (Box 363)
          Catalog # EMDS-6503; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6503-A
          Emergency Records
        - Morel, George - Coke dj-culture, 2004; SR-22474; Morel, George; Rodigan, David (Box 363)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 54490 1A1
          Coke Dj-culture
        - Morel, George - Morel's grooves pt. 9, 1995; SR-22475; Morel, George (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22476. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SR 12384; A-side Matrix # SR-12384-BOYS+GIRLS
          Strictly Rhythm
        - Morel, George - Morel's grooves pt. 9, 1995; SR-22476; Morel, George (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22475. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SR 12384; A-side Matrix # SR-12384-BODY
        - Morenas - Hazme soñar, 1990; SR-22477; Morenas (Box 363)
          Catalog # DFC 020; A-side Matrix # DFC 020-LL
          Dance Floor Corporation
        - Morenas - Hazme soñar, 1990; SR-22478; Morenas (Box 363)
        - Morgan, Denroy - Sweet tender love, 1981; SR-22479; Morgan, Denroy (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22480. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BKD 506; A-side Matrix # BKD-506-A
          Becket Records
        - Morgan, Denroy - Sweet tender love, 1981; SR-22480; Morgan, Denroy (Box 363)
          In same jacket as # SR-22479. 2 copies.
        - Morgan, Denroy - High on your love, 1983; SR-22481; Morgan, Denroy (Box 363)
          Catalog # BKD 514; A-side Matrix # BKD-514-A-X
        - Morgan, Denroy - Everybody wants to be somebody else, 1984; SR-22482; Morgan, Denroy (Box 364)
          Catalog # JD-14117; A-side Matrix # PW-14117C-1
        - Morgan, Denroy - Give it to me, 1987; SR-22483; Morgan, Denroy (Box 364)
          Catalog # SUD 059; A-side Matrix # SUD 059 DJA C1
          Sutra
        - Morgan, Denroy - I'll do anything for you | Inner city blues | You're my everything, 2005; SR-22484; Morgan, Denroy; Gaye, Marvin; Esmeralda, Santa (Box 364)
          Catalog # MDC 681; A-side Matrix # MDC 681 A
          Mass Dance Classics
        - Morgan, Meli'sa - Do me baby, 1985; SR-22485; Morgan, Meli'sa (Box 364)
          Catalog # V-15211; A-side Matrix # V-1-15211-100000-A Z1
        - Morgan, Meli'sa - Still in love with you, 1992; SR-22486; Morgan, Meli'sa (Box 364)
          Catalog # 0-66438; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66438-A-1-DMM
          Pendulum Records
        - Morgan, Meli'sa - Fool's paradise, 1986; SR-22487; Morgan, Meli'sa (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22488. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO-9730; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9730-99998-A
        - Morgan, Meli'sa - Fool's paradise, 1986; SR-22488; Morgan, Meli'sa (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22487. 2 copies.
        - Morganics - Evolve (selected tracks), 2003; SR-22489; Morganics (Box 364)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # AE 536563/A
          Australia
        - Moroder, Giorgio - Music from "Battlestar Galactica" and other original compositions, 1978; SR-22490; Moroder, Giorgio (Box 364)
          Catalog # NBLP 7126; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7126-AS
        - Moroder, Giorgio - Evolution | Street player, 2000; SR-22491; Moroder, Giorgio; Chicago (Box 364)
          Catalog # 0.00208333333333333; A-side Matrix # #0.03-A
          Rated "X" Records
        - Morris Black & Co - Keep it up; Flying, 1991; SR-22492; Morris Black & Co (Box 364)
          Catalog # FTM 31685; A-side Matrix # FTM31685 A
          London Street
          Rome, Italy
        - Morris, David - Saturday night, 1982; SR-22493; Morris, David (Box 364)
          Catalog # BKD 509; A-side Matrix # BKD-509-A
        - Morrison, Junie - Tease me, 1984; SR-22494; Morrison, Junie (Box 364)
          Catalog # DMD 793; A-side Matrix # STDM 47039 46864-2
        - Morrison, Junie - Techno-freqs, 1984; SR-22495; Morrison, Junie (Box 364)
          Catalog # PRO 404; A-side Matrix # STDM 46276-2
        - Morrison, Mark - Return of the Mack, 1996; SR-22496; Morrison, Mark (Box 364)
          Catalog # 0630-14587-1; A-side Matrix # WMME ALSDORF 063 014587-1-A2
        - Morrison, Mark - Moan & groan, 1997; SR-22497; Morrison, Mark (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22498. Different discs.
          Catalog # SAM 1974; A-side Matrix # SAM 1974 A
        - Morrison, Mark - Let's get down, 1995; SR-22498; Morrison, Mark (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22497. Different discs.
          Catalog # SAM 1659; A-side Matrix # SAM 1659-A1
        - Morton, Paul S - God's got those healing hands, 1990; SR-22499; Morton, Paul S; Greater St Stephen Baptist Church BC Mass Choir (Box 364)
          Catalog # GCR 4035; A-side Matrix # GSS-1001-A
          Gospel Capital Records
        - Mos Def - Ms. Fat Booty; Mathematics, 1999; SR-22500; Mos Def (Box 364)
          Catalog # SPRO 81276; A-side Matrix # 08724-81276-2-1-A
        - Mos Def - Respiration, 1999; SR-22501; Mos Def; Kweli, Talib; Black Star (Box 364)
          Catalog # SPRO 81169; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81169-A
        - Mos Def - Oh no (DJ hype remix), 2000; SR-22502; Mos Def; Nate Dogg; Monch, Pharoahe (Box 364)
          Catalog # RWK303T; A-side Matrix # RWK 303T A-1
        - Mos Def - Sunshine, 2005; SR-22503; Mos Def (Box 364)
          Catalog # GEFR-11379-1; A-side Matrix # GEFR-11379-1 A
        - Mos Def - Black on both sides (disc one), 2006; SR-22504; Mos Def (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22505; SR-22506. Double album.
          Catalog # RWK-1159; A-side Matrix # RWK-1159A
        - Mos Def - Black on both sides (disc two), 2006; SR-22505; Mos Def (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22504; SR-22506. Double album.
          Catalog # RWK-1159; A-side Matrix # RWK-1159C
        - Lost Boyz - Love, peace, and nappiness, 1997; SR-22506; Lost Boyz (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22504; SR-22505. Different discs.
          Catalog # U-53072; A-side Matrix # U-53072
        - Most, Don - 33rd degree manslaughter, 1999; SR-22507; Most, Don (Box 364)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 030899-A
          100 Proof Enterprise
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - Most Requested Rhythm Band - Got to give it up, 1978; SR-22508; Most Requested Rhythm Band (Box 364)
          Catalog # MD-114; A-side Matrix # MD114-A
          Magic Disc Records
        - Motels - Shock, 1985; SR-22509; Motels (Box 364)
          Catalog # SPRO-9515; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9515-99906-Z2
        - Moten, Wendy - Step by step, 1992; SR-22510; Moten, Wendy (Box 364)
          Catalog # SPRO-04890; A-side Matrix # SPRO-04890-A
        - Mother Earth - Stoned woman, 1992; SR-22511; Mother Earth (Box 364)
          Catalog # JAZID LP48; A-side Matrix # JAZIDLP-48-A
          Acid Jazz
        - Mother Night - Mother night, 1972; SR-22512; Mother Night (Box 364)
          Catalog # KC 31304; A-side Matrix # AL-31304 1E
        - Mother's Finest - Subluxation, 1990; SR-22513; Mother's Finest (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22514. Different discs.
          Catalog # PL74836; A-side Matrix # 009 DMD-7808 A-1 C
        - Mother's Finest - Subluxation, 1990; SR-22514; Mother's Finest (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22513. Different discs.
          Catalog # PT44128; A-side Matrix # 009 DMD-7816 A-1
        - Motion - The trilogy pt. 1 (3MC'z) (we don't #@!* around) | Reloaded, 2001; SR-22515; Motion; UBAD (Box 364)
          Catalog # BLK 888; A-side Matrix # BLK 888 A
          Blacklist Music
          Toronto, Canada
        - Motion Unit - Copper, 2001; SR-22516; Motion Unit; Garp (Box 364)
          Catalog # 74321 88525 1; A-side Matrix # B151633-01 A1 KR
        - Motor City Crew - Let's break, 1983; SR-22517; Motor City Crew (Box 364)
          Catalog # 4513MGA; A-side Matrix # 4513MG-A-66866-D-15A
        - Motown Sounds - Space dance, 1978; SR-22518; Motown Sounds (Box 364)
          Catalog # M7-908R1; A-side Matrix # M7-908 R1A
        - Mott the Hoople - Mott the Hoople live, 1974; SR-22519; Mott the Hoople (Box 364)
          Catalog # PC 33282; A-side Matrix # P AL-33282-3B
        - Motta, Ed - Um jantar pra dois, 1990; SR-22520; Motta, Ed; Bombom (Box 364)
          Catalog # 6WP.2025; A-side Matrix # 6WP.2025-A
        - Motta, Ed - Um contrato com deus, 1990; SR-22521; Motta, Ed (Box 364)
          Catalog # 670.8145; A-side Matrix # 670.8145-A
        - Motta, Ed - Solução (remix) | Todo o meu ouro (remix), 1990; SR-22522; Motta, Ed; Kid Abelha E Os Abóboras Selvagens (Box 364)
          Catalog # 6WP.2014; A-side Matrix # 6WP.2014-A
        - Motta, Ed - Parada de Lucas | Projeto de lei, 1989; SR-22523; Motta, Ed; Conexao Japeri; Luni (Box 364)
          Catalog # 6WP.1059; A-side Matrix # 6WP.1059-A
        - Motta, Zezé - Zezé Motta, 1978; SR-22524; Motta, Zezé (Box 364)
          Catalog # LP-S-39-57; A-side Matrix # LPS-39-57-A
        - Motto, Denise - Tell Jack (jack the house), 1987; SR-22525; Motto, Denise (Box 364)
          Catalog # LEFT 9T; A-side Matrix # LEFT 9T A1
          Rhythm King Records
        - Mottola, Tony - I only have eyes for you, 1975; SR-22526; Mottola, Tony (Box 364)
          Catalog # PR 5094 SD; A-side Matrix # 5094 SDA-1
          Project 3 Records
        - Mount Rushmore - You better, 1999; SR-22527; Mount Rushmore; Knack (Box 364)
          Catalog # MCST40192; A-side Matrix # MCST 40192 A-1-1
          Universal
        - Mouskouri, Nana - Concert '80 (das live-doppelalbum), 1980; SR-22528; Mouskouri, Nana (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22529. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 9198 809; A-side Matrix # 10 AA9198809 1Y
          Philips
        - Mouskouri, Nana - Concert '80 (das live-doppelalbum), 1980; SR-22529; Mouskouri, Nana (Box 364)
          In same jacket as # SR-22528. 2 copies.
        - Mouzon, Alphonse - Love, fantasy, 1987; SR-22530; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 364)
          Catalog # MPC 6001; A-side Matrix # MPC 6001-A
          MPC Records
        - Mouzon, Alphonse - I'm glad that you're here, 1981; SR-22531; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 364)
          Catalog # HLX 10581; A-side Matrix # HLX 10581 A
          London Records
        - Mouzon, Alphonse - The essence of mystery, 1973; SR-22532; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 364)
          Catalog # BN-LA059-F; A-side Matrix # BN-LA059-E1-1
          Blue Note
        - Move - Greedy girls, 1986; SR-22533; Move (Box 364)
          Catalog # SUN 442; A-side Matrix # SUN-442-A-RE
        - Movement - Movement, 1986; SR-22534; Movement (Box 364)
          Catalog # AP 123; A-side Matrix # AP 123 AS
          Underworld Records
        - Movement Ex - Freedom got a shotgun, 1990; SR-22535; Movement Ex (Box 364)
          Catalog # 44 73525; A-side Matrix # XSS 73525B-1A
        - Movies - She gave me that itch, 1987; SR-22536; Movies (Box 364)
          Catalog # MRC-1039; A-side Matrix # L11130 MRC-1039-A
          Macola Record Co
        - Movin' Melodies - Don't play back, 1996; SR-22537; Movin' Melodies (Box 365)
          Catalog # MMR 010; A-side Matrix # MMR010-THIS SIDE
          Movin' Melodies
        - Moyet, Alison - Weak in the presence of beauty, 1987; SR-22538; Moyet, Alison (Box 365)
          Catalog # 44 06940; A-side Matrix # XSS-176215-1A
        - Moz-Art - Let the music move me (remix), 1991; SR-22539; Moz-Art; Master Freeze (Box 365)
          Catalog # OZ 010; A-side Matrix # OZ-010 A
        - Moz-Art - Let the music move me, 1991; SR-22540; Moz-Art; Master Freeze (Box 365)
          Catalog # OZ 006; A-side Matrix # OZ-006-A
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus - Mozart edicion bicentenario (disc one), 1990; SR-22541; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22542; SR-22543. Triple album.
          Catalog # LP-7000; A-side Matrix # LP-7000-A IN3-DMI
          Sarpe
          Spain
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus - Mozart edicion bicentenario (disc two), 1990; SR-22542; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22541; SR-22543. Triple album.
          Catalog # LP-7000; A-side Matrix # LP-7001-A IN3-DMI
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus - Mozart edicion bicentenario (disc three), 1990; SR-22543; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22541; SR-22542. Triple album.
          Catalog # LP-7000; A-side Matrix # LP-7002-A IN3-DMI
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus - Eine kleine nachtmusik, 1962; SR-22544; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus; Czech Chamber Orchestra (Box 365)
          Catalog # PLPS-163; A-side Matrix # PLPS-163A
          Parliament Records Corporation
        - Mputu, Dely - Je préfère balancer la sauce, 1988; SR-22545; Mputu, Dely (Box 365)
          Catalog # VL 1; A-side Matrix # VL 1 A
          Anvers Musique
        - Mr. Big Mouse - Drop that ghetto blaster, 1989; SR-22546; Mr. Big Mouse (Box 365)
          Catalog # 12SSR90; A-side Matrix # 12 SSR 90-A1
          SSR Records
          Brussels, Belgium
        - Mr. Biggs - Standing on the verge, 1989; SR-22547; Mr. Biggs (Box 365)
          Catalog # PW 441; A-side Matrix # A-1-PW-441-A
        - Mr. Bristle - The Mr. Bristle EP, 1999; SR-22548; Mr. Bristle (Box 365)
          Catalog # GG1014; A-side Matrix # GR-1014-A
          Gossip Records
        - Mr. C the Slide Man - Cha-cha slide, 2000; SR-22549; Mr. C the Slide Man (Box 365)
          Catalog # 012 158 378-1; A-side Matrix # 012158378-1 A
        - Mr. C the Slide Man - Cha-cha slide, 2000; SR-22550; Mr. C the Slide Man (Box 365)
        - Mr. Cheeks - Crush on you; The wire, 2003; SR-22551; Mr. Cheeks (Box 365)
          Catalog # UNIR 20930-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR 20930-1A
        - Mr. Cheeks - Lights, camera, action!, 2001; SR-22552; Mr. Cheeks (Box 365)
          Catalog # 440 015 135-1; A-side Matrix # 440 015 135 1 A
        - Mr. Comicstore - The theme of comics, 2006; SR-22553; Mr. Comicstore (Box 365)
          Catalog # MMSI-001; A-side Matrix #
          Mamushi Records
        - Mr. D Original - New #1 record, SR-22554; Mr. D Original; Crew Original (Box 365)
          Catalog # MR6102-1; A-side Matrix # MR-6102-A
          Money Entertainment
        - Mr. D Original - Absolutely, SR-22555; Mr. D Original; Crew Original (Box 365)
          Catalog # MR 6103; A-side Matrix # MC-6-MR6103-R A
        - Mr. Dibbs - 231 ways to fry an egg, 1988; SR-22556; Mr. Dibbs (Box 365)
          Catalog # 4WR 942-1202; A-side Matrix # FW 942-1202-A
          Four Ways to Rock
          Montreal, Ontario
        - Mr. Dibbs - Unearthed vol 1, 1997; SR-22557; Mr. Dibbs (Box 365)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 400020-A
          Phat Head Records
        - Mr. Fiddler - Cool about it, 1990; SR-22558; Mr. Fiddler (Box 365)
          Catalog # ED 5486; A-side Matrix # STED-5486-A1
        - Mr. Fiddler - Cool about it, 1990; SR-22559; Mr. Fiddler (Box 365)
          Catalog # ED 5503; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5503 A-1
        - Mr. Fingers - Washing machine, 1986; SR-22560; Mr. Fingers (Box 365)
          Catalog # TX127; A-side Matrix # TX-127-A
        - Mr. Freeze and the Homewreckers - We're compatible, 1993; SR-22561; Mr. Freeze and the Homewreckers (Box 365)
          Catalog # 70002-1; A-side Matrix # 7002-1-A
        - Mr. Freeze and the Homewreckers - Phat EP, 1992; SR-22562; Mr. Freeze and the Homewreckers (Box 365)
          Catalog # T 2001 PHAT EP; A-side Matrix # RADT-2001-A
        - M.K. Fresh Connection - Positioned for the kill, 1991; SR-22563; M.K. Fresh Connection (Box 365)
          Catalog # AVCD-1005; A-side Matrix # AVJD 1005 A 1Y1 0991
          Avex Trax
          Tokyo, Japan
        - Mr. Lif - Live from the plantation; Return of the b-boy, 2003; SR-22564; Mr. Lif (Box 365)
          Catalog # DJX045; A-side Matrix # DJX045-1A
          Definitive Jux
        - Mr. Magic - Magic's message, 1984; SR-22565; Mr. Magic (Box 365)
          Catalog # POS 1213; A-side Matrix # POS-1213-A-1796
          Posse Records
        - Mr. Marcelo - How you like it, 2000; SR-22566; Mr. Marcelo; Master P (Box 365)
          Catalog # SPRO 81365; A-side Matrix # S-43313
          Tuff Guys Entertainment
        - Mr. Mike - Texas 2000, 1999; SR-22567; Mr. Mike (Box 365)
          Catalog # SPRO 81205; A-side Matrix # S-41120
        - Mr. Oizo - Flat beat, 1999; SR-22568; Mr. Oizo (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22569. 2 copies.
          Catalog # F 104; A-side Matrix # DFI-99.2 F 104 A1
          F Communications
        - Mr. Oizo - Flat beat, 1999; SR-22569; Mr. Oizo (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22568. 2 copies.
        - Mr. On - Breathe don't stop, 2004; SR-22570; Mr. On; Jungle Brothers (Box 365)
          Catalog # UL 1198-6; A-side Matrix # UL-1198-A
          Ultra Records
        - Mr. Pink - Payin' the price | Death before dishonor, 1996; SR-22571; Mr. Pink; Mr. Blonde (Box 365)
          Catalog # BP1; A-side Matrix # BP1-A1
          Reservoir Records
        - Mr. Q - D.J. style, 1979; SR-22572; Mr. Q (Box 365)
          Catalog # DK 18; A-side Matrix # DK-18-A
          Monica's Production
        - Mr. Q - Party party, 1979; SR-22573; Mr. Q (Box 365)
          Catalog # D.K. 20; A-side Matrix # DK-20-A
        - Mr. Q - Love & time, 1979; SR-22574; Mr. Q (Box 365)
          Catalog # D.K. 19; A-side Matrix # DK-19-A
          D.K. Sound's
        - Mr. Rhymes - Stop breakin, 1986; SR-22575; Mr. Rhymes (Box 365)
          Catalog # GSS 001; A-side Matrix # GSS-001-A
          V.I.P. Records
        - Mr. Rhymes - Stop breakin, 1986; SR-22576; Mr. Rhymes (Box 365)
        - Mr. Rumble - Whoomp! ... There it is, 2001; SR-22577; Mr. Rumble; Brasstooth; Kee (Box 365)
          Catalog # CENT 16T; A-side Matrix # 08 45459 20 1B1 RUMBLE 1
          Incentive
        - Mr. Schnabel - Is'n schnabelding - das instrumental album (disc one), 2001; SR-22578; Mr. Schnabel (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22579. Double album.
          Catalog # SHOW1005-1; A-side Matrix # B146898-01 A1 MK
          Showdown
        - Mr. Schnabel - Is'n schnabelding - das instrumental album (disc two), 2001; SR-22579; Mr. Schnabel (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22578. Double album.
          Catalog # SHOW1005-1; A-side Matrix # B146898-02 C1 MK
        - Mr. Scruff - Mr. Scruff (disc one), 1997; SR-22580; Mr. Scruff (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22581. Double album.
          Catalog # JOY13; A-side Matrix # JOY 13 A-01-01-1
          Pleasure Music
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Mr. Scruff - Mr. Scruff (disc two), 1997; SR-22581; Mr. Scruff (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22580. Double album.
          Catalog # JOY13; A-side Matrix # JOY 13 C-01-01-1
        - Mr. Scruff - Sweetsmoke, 2002; SR-22582; Mr. Scruff (Box 365)
          Catalog # ZEN 12124; A-side Matrix # ZEN12124A-1
          Ninja Tune
        - Mr. Serv-On - My best friend, 1997; SR-22583; Mr. Serv-On (Box 365)
          Catalog # SPRO 30183; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30183-A
        - Mr. Serv-On - From N.Y. to N.O., 1999; SR-22584; Mr. Serv-On; Mr. Servon (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22585. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 81168; A-side Matrix # S-40308
        - Mr. Serv-On - From N.Y. to N.O., 1999; SR-22585; Mr. Serv-On; Mr. Servon (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22584. 2 copies.
        - Mr. Smith - Mr. Smith's DJ tools, 2001; SR-22586; Mr. Smith (Box 365)
          Catalog # 6614 MR-002-1; A-side Matrix # 6614-MR002-1
        - Mr. Smith - Here comes the rain; Faith, 2001; SR-22587; Mr. Smith (Box 365)
          Catalog # 6614 MR-004-1; A-side Matrix # 6614-MR004-1 CA1
        - Mr Spring - Voyager 1.56, 1998; SR-22588; Mr Spring (Box 365)
          Catalog # SVDJ 002; A-side Matrix # SVDJ-002-A
          Manifesto
        - Mr. Vegas - How about that; Gal them, 2001; SR-22589; Mr. Vegas (Box 365)
          Catalog # GAP004; A-side Matrix # GAP-004 A1
          Greensleeves Records
        - Mr. X - One time (at my door), 1995; SR-22590; Mr. X (Box 365)
          Catalog # JUNG-5001-1; A-side Matrix # JUNG 5001-1-A
          Jungle Records
          Culver City, California